Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS 202
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Prints by theme
  - Subseries B: Events
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Fountain at night
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Head phones
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: PS 1
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: "Ronnie Cutrone's friend Walter…SoHo Saturdays"
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Interior with television
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Television Crew
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Man with monitor
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Gun shots
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: "Ray - o - gram"
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Foot inside shirt
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
  - Subseries C: Landscape
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Landscape
      Number of Items: 12
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Altered Landscape
  - Subseries D: Paper Collage
    Box 7 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Description: parts for Collage
      Process: 5x7 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Description: "Boys "
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Gym Shorts Oval
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Broken Ovals
    - Title: Wrapper (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Sit Ups
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Dalmation
      Process: 11x14 Dye Bleach Transfer
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Figure from "Desire" series
      Process: 8x10 Dye Bleach Transfer
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Figure negative block head
    - Title: Rock and column (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Process: 7x14 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Description: Figure red X
      Process: 16x20 Cibachrome
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Description: Figure X
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Sanctity
      Process: 11x17 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Statue
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Faith dinosaur
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Description: Four stars
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Description: Condom Figure globe
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Description: Figure for Guitar
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Description: Saluki cut out
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: Experiment for Torso
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: Similar to Pom Poms
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: 1919
  - Subseries E: Portrait
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Description: Astor, Patti
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Process: 16x20 Color C-Print
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Description: Cutrone, Ronnie
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Description: Eno, Brian
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Description: Mitchel, Eric
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Title:, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Description: Ono, Yoko
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Description: Acconci, Vito
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Description: Bourdon, David
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Description: Byrne, David
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
      Description: Countess
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
      Description: Curtis, Jackie
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Description: Delight, Duca
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Description: "Gi Gi"
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Description: Hannah, Duncan
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Description: Harrison, Jerry
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Description: Loud, Lance
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 45)
      Description: Hell, Richard
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Description: Mr. Peanut
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 47)
      Description: Mumps
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Description: Paik, Nam June
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Description: Rivers, Larry
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 49)
      Description: "Ron" also labeled Sebastian
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Description: Sellers, Terence
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 51)
      Description: Smith, Jack
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 52)
      Description: Stefanotty, Robert and Maralee Johnson
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Description: Talking Heads
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
      Description: White, James Chance
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Description: Wilson, May
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Description: Unidentified Man
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Description: Unidentified man
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Description: Unidentified man -Hitler pose
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 58)
      Description: Unidentified Men
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Description: Tucker, Marcia
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Description: Unidentified Woman
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
      Description: Nudeback, Gail
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Description: Unknown Woman
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Alessandra Gallery
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory, David Bourdon, and Hilton Kramer
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory, David Bourdon, Robert Steffanotty, Rosalind Krauss, Barbara Rose, Annette Michaelson, Hilton Kramer
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Brahms, Peter
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Burroughs, William, John Giorno, and Laurie Anderson
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Byron
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Churicova Inverse, Inna
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Coogan
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Cortez, Diego
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Dali, Salvador and Gregory Battcock
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy and Jimmy Jr
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Goodman, Ken
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Grief, Paula
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Harry, Debbie
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Hell, Richard - fragment
      Process: 4x8 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Idol, Billy
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Johnson, Ray
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: McCabe, Tom
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Nervous Breakdown
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Panfilov, Gleb
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Rosenblum, Robert and Jane Kaplowitz
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified subjects
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Saluki with unidentified subjects
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Smith, Patti - concert
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Smith, Rupert
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Teenage Jesus and the Jerks
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Varbie, Stephen
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: "Victor Hugo"
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Warhol, Andy and "Victor Hugo"
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Winters, Robin
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Cropped portrait
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Hands
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified Band
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentfied Band
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified nude female subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified Subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Hats
      Number of Items: 31
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Giraffe
    - Title: (Box 12)
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Flamigo
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Ship
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Sink
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Joseph Kennedy House - Palm Beach
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: "Miami Florida" labeled on back by Laurie Simmons
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Street Scene
      Process: 6x7 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Palm tree
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Two boys
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Umbrella
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Dark image, male nude?
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Painting Documentation
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Six headshots of a boy
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Assorted male and female subjects, books
      Process: Polaroid
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: Tina Summerlin Photo
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: "Mario Monte - Star of Jack Smith's 'Normal Love'"
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: Unidentitfied Subjects
      Process: 11x14 Color C-Print
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 70)
      Description: Ney Tait Fraser photograph
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 70)
      Description: Unknown photographer
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Description: Diego Cortez photo, Herman Dahled, Jon Rudd, Pierre Dahled, Winston Spriet, Brux
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Description: Chris Stein photograph, Iggy Pop and Debbie Harry
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 72)
      Description: Roberta Bayley photograph, Jimmy de Sana, Diego Cortez, and Anya Phillips
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 72)
      Description: Lizbeth Mariano photograph
  - Subseries G: Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 14)
      Description: Paintings, sculptures, drawings and gallery interiors
      Number of Items: 58
    - Title: (Box 15)
      Description: Paintings, drawings, sculptures and gallery interiors
      Number of Items: 55
    - Title: (Box 16)
      Number of Items: 44
- Series III: Slides by project
  General note
  ***As of 23 February 2010, this Series is unavailable to researchers.***
  - Subseries A: Submission
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Cigarrette
      Process: Color Transparency Slide
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Harness
      Number of Items: 7
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Mask with tube
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Beach
  - Subseries B: Early Sex
    - Title: Aluminum Foil, 1980 (Box 17)
      Description: Aluminum Foil
      Number of Items: 111
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Antlers and plywood; Darrell Bagley model
      Number of Items: 39
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Apples, Toilet - Urine theme
      Number of Items: 16
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Artichoke - Urine theme
    - Title: (Box 17)
      Description: Astroturf
      Number of Items: 159
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 17)
      Description: Athletic Tape shoot
      Process: 4x5 Color Transparency
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 17)
      Number of Items: 72
    - Title: Auto, 1980 (Box 17)
      Description: Auto
      Number of Items: 49
    - Title: Balloons (Box 18)
      Description: Balloons, Darrel Bagley model
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bathtub Suicide
      Number of Items: 32
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bathtub Suicide (Red)
      Number of Items: 70
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bathroom Red - Jimmy De Sana
      Number of Items: 26
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Beach and beachballs
      Number of Items: 35
    - Title: Giant Beachball, 1982 (Box 18)
      Description: Beachball
    - Title: Giant Beachball, 1982 (Box 18)
      Number of Items: 69
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Beachballs; beachballs, sneakers, in a glade
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: "Bed Two Figures Blue"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 18)
      Description: Bed - female
      Number of Items: 15
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bed (jump)
      Number of Items: 38
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bed, Jump on bed
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: Bed, Between Mattresses with Plant
      Number of Items: 13
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 18)
      Description: "Bicycle in a landscape Model: Jimmy de Sana"
      Number of Items: 11
    - Title: (Box 18)
      Description: Bottles
      Number of Items: 93
    - Title: Box, 1983 (Box 18)
      Description: Box
      Number of Items: 30
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: Camouflage at the beach
      Number of Items: 18
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: Candy Corn
      Number of Items: 37
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: Cantaloupe
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 19)
      Description: Cardboard
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 19)
      Description: Celery shoot
      Number of Items: 91
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: "Cereal in bathtub Jimmy de Sana model"
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 19)
      Description: "Chair Shoot Laurie Simmons at Robert Kitchen's"
      Number of Items: 10
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 19)
      Description: Chocolate syrup, half body shoot
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 19)
      Description: Cigarette shoot, brick wall
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 19)
      Description: Clarence Flexing
      Number of Items: 43
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: Clarence on Astroturf
      Number of Items: 9
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 19)
      Description: "Coat Hanger shoot Laurie Simmons and Jimmy de Sana models"
      Number of Items: 76
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 19)
      Description: "Coffee Table Laurie Simmons model"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Title: Condom, 1979 (Box 19)
      Description: Condom (stove)
    - Title: Contact Paper, 1980 (Box 19)
      Description: Contact Paper (red check Figure - Laurie on Blue couch)
    - Title: Cowboy Boots (Box 19)
      Description: Cowboy Boots
    - Title: Coyote (Box 19)
      Description: "Coyote Silver Mask in Forest shoot"
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: "Cucumber Red bathroom"
      Number of Items: 27
    - Title: (Box 19)
      Description: Deck
    - Title: Dishwasher, 1979 (Box 20)
      Description: Dishwasher
    - Title: Dishwasher, 1979 (Box 20)
      Number of Items: 21
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 20)
      Description: Egg
      Number of Items: 14
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 20)
      Description: Eggs
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: Enema (over bathtub)
      Number of Items: 40
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: Enema Blue bathroom
    - Title: Extension Cord, 1979 (Box 20)
      Description: Extension Cord
      Number of Items: 6
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: Fire - penis wick
    - Title: Fur Coat (Box 20)
      Description: "Fur Coat outside shoot "
    - Title: Gauze, 1979 (Box 20)
      Description: Gauze
    - Title: Gauze, 1979 (Box 20)
      Number of Items: 47
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 20)
      Description: Gauze shoot
      Number of Items: 22
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 20)
      Description: Green Shower; Green bathroom with blowup doll
      Number of Items: 33
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: Greenwich - Labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: Gun, Backseat, Bullet Belt
    - Title:, 1983 (Box 20)
      Description: H L
      Number of Items: 50
    - Title: (Box 20)
      Description: H.L. - similar Male yellow spots on chest
      Number of Items: 75
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Hallway Bondage
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 21)
      Description: Hallway Bondage suit
      Number of Items: 25
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Helmet
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 21)
      Description: High Heel
    - Title: Iguana, 1979 (Box 21)
      Description: "Iguana "
    - Title: Iguana, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Ketchup
      Number of Items: 20
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 21)
      Description: "Kitchen bondage "
    - Title: Ladder, 1980 (Box 21)
      Description: Ladder
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Lampshade
      Number of Items: 28
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 21)
      Description: Laurie Simmons and Jimmy de Sana models, couch
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 21)
      Description: Laurie Simmons and Paula Grief, bathtub, pink light
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 21)
      Description: Laurie Simmons and Paula Grief, bathtub, white
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 21)
      Description: Laurie Simmons at Robert Kitchen’s swimming pool
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Laurie Simmons fur and red chair shoot
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Leaves, bathtub
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Lights, figure in bed
    - Title: Marker Cones, 1982 (Box 21)
      Description: Marker Cones
    - Title: Marker Cones, 1982 (Box 21)
      Number of Items: 29
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Mink Stole
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Nantucket Sex
      Number of Items: 90
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Nantucket Sex, Two nudes - in a canoe
    - Title: (Box 21)
      Description: Nike shoot
    - Title: Plastic Bags, 1980 (Box 22)
      Description: Plastic Bags
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 22)
      Description: Plastic Wrap
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 22)
      Description: Pliers
    - Title: Pocket Book, 1979 (Box 22)
      Description: "Pocket Book Purse female"
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 22)
      Description: "Pool shoot Laurie Simmons model at Robert Kitchen's pool"
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 22)
      Number of Items: 59
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 22)
      Description: "Purse shoe shoot purse head, “shoe”"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 22)
      Description: "Purse, head, outdoors Laurie Simmons model"
      Number of Items: 57
    - Title: (Box 22)
      Description: Purse, Head, Wood Panelling
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Title: (Box 22)
      Description: Ribbon
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 22)
      Description: Sea Shell
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 22)
      Description: "Seashell (Conch shell)"
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 22)
      Description: Seashells and Eggshells
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 22)
      Number of Items: 135
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving Cream (bathtub)
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving Cream (ceiling)
      Number of Items: 24
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving Cream (red)
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving Cream (red, square)
      Number of Items: 66
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving Cream, same shoot as Gas Cans
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Shaving male Nude on beach
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Shoe (Beach)
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Shoe Nylons
    - Title: Shoes, 1979 (Box 23)
      Description: Shoes - dining table
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Silver Mask
      Number of Items: 197
    - Title: Sink, 1979 (Box 23)
      Description: Sink - Transvestite
    - Title: (Box 23)
      Description: Slinkies shoot
      Number of Items: 67
    - Title: Soap Suds, 1980 (Box 23)
      Description: Soap Suds
    - Title: Soap Suds, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Title: Boxes, 1980 (Box 23)
      Description: Storage Boxes
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 23)
      Description: Sweatshirt shoot
    - Title: Telephone Wire, 1979 (Box 24)
      Description: Telephone Wire
    - Title: (Box 24)
      Description: Thimbles
      Number of Items: 36
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 24)
      Description: Toothpaste
      Number of Items: 71
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 24)
      Description: Track: Female runner
    - Title: Travel Bags (Box 24)
      Description: Travel Bags
    - Title: Travel Bags (Box 24)
    - Title: (Box 24)
      Description: Trunk
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 24)
      Description: "Tube shoot Black Catheter Ocean"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 24)
      Description: Tube, female bathtub
      Number of Items: 23
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 24)
      Description: Underwear shoot
    - Title: Untitled (Suit, 1980 (Box 24)
      Description: Untitled Suit (Instant Camera)
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 24)
      Description: Warm Up Suit
      Number of Items: 157
    - Title:, 1978 (Box 24)
      Description: Watermelon shoot
  - Subseries C: $bfat
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Bubble Gum Re-shoot"
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Cowboy Hat Experiment Blue"
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Cowboy Hat Re-shoot"
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Dalmatian at beach Re-shoot"
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: Jimmy Jr. in Pants shoot
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: Dalmatian
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 25)
      Description: Pants pink
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Pants Twins Rephotographed "
    - Title: (Box 25)
      Description: "Pink Light Two men hang from ceiling"
  - Subseries D: $dobjects
    - Title: Aluminum Foil, 1985 (Box 26)
      Description: Aluminum Foil (couple)
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Black Cat
    - Title: Crackers, 1985 (Box 26)
      Description: Crackers
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Easter Chicks
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Flour
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Foam; Blue
      Number of Items: 17
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Garlic Skins Shoot
      Number of Items: 48
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Geometric Cones
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Ketchup and Mustard
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Macaroni shoot
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Oranges
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Pipecleaner
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Popcorn shoot
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: PVC pipe
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Ravioli
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Samples shoot
      Number of Items: 56
    - Title: (Box 26)
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Socks
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: "Shoe Tree"
    - Title: String, 1987 (Box 26)